Javiera Moreno /

Associate

Practice Area: Litigation

javiera.moreno@ocl.cl

Javiera's experience is in Judicial area, specializing in litigation, dispute resolution and arbitration. She has sound experience in civil, commercial and consumer matters and has been a participant in different international events on the protection of personal information and digital rights.

WORK HISTORY

2017 - present / Ovalle Consejeros Legales

2013 - 2016 / Puelma y Cía.

2009 - 2010 / Bofill Mir & Álvarez Hinzpeter Jana Abogados

EXPERIENCE

- Participant in the Protected Information Foundation for the defense of digital rights, privacy and personal data protection.
- Speaker on digital rights, privacy and personal data protection at international congresses.

EDUCATION

B.A. in Legal and Social Sciences, graduating cum laude, University of Chile. Admissions: 2015.

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

- Aid in Legal Clinics, School of Law, University of Chile
- Litigant and Speaker, Protected Data Foundation.

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/javieram/